xandria.com 2007-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Xandria Collection

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. We, therefore, feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of information on our website. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to us by email or phone. If we do not respond to your inquiry or do not address it in a satisfactory manner, please contact TRUSTe (<http://www.truste.org/users/watchdog.html>). 

Information We Collect and How It's Used  
Sharing of Information  
Security  
External Links  
Changes  
Deletions and Opt-Out  
Glossary of Terms  
Adult Video Compliance  
Contact Information

**Information You Provide Directly To Us...**

**...via Order Form**  
To process your order, we require your name, billing address, phone number, email address (If you want to receive and e-mail confirmation of your order), shipping address and credit card information. We use this information to process your order and, if any questions should arise, to contact you about your order. In general, we will try to contact you first by email and only if that fails, or if time is critical, will we try to contact you by phone. We share this information, and only that information which is absolutely necessary, with those third parties that are involved in the processing of your order. For example, the financial institution that issued your credit card and the shipping carrier that delivers your order. If you supply us with your postal address in this manner, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, place the text **DO NOT MAIL** in the comment section of the billing page. If you have previously placed an order and do not wish to receive any mailing, please follow our opt-out instructions. 

**...via Email**  
Should you decide to contact us via email, we will use your email address solely to send you a reply. 

**...via Promotional E-mail Lists**   
You may receive special promotional offers via e-mail from Xandria.com should you choose to. Membership on this list is optional and requires your consent via a check box in the Xandria.com shopping cart. You may unsubscribe from this list at any time. 

**...via Newsletter Subscription**  
We make available an email newsletter and should you decide to subscribe, we will send you newsletter announcements from time to time until you unsubscribe. Subscription to our newsletter is optional and requires your consent via our newsletter subscription form. 

**...via Sweepstakes Entry Form**  
To enter any of our contests, we require your name, mailing address, and email address. Should you be a winner, we will notify you via email and prize redemption instructions will be sent via postal mail to the address you gave us with your entry form. We will not use your personal information for any other purpose, but you may receive additional e-mailings. 

**...via Polls**  
Our optional online surveys ask visitors for demographic information such as relationship status to show in aggregate how our users feel about various issues. This information is not linked to any other personal or identifying information. 

**...via Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, and message boards, available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. We recemmend not disclosing personal information online. 

**Session ID:**   
Upon visiting our site, we assign you a unique Session ID and attempt to store that onto your computer in the form of a cookie. This is used to keep track of your shopping basket during your visit and between visits. If you do not wish to have even a one-time Session ID assigned, we recommend that you place your order by phone, fax or postal mail. 

**IP Address:**   
We record IP addresses in the aggregate for monitoring the level of activity on our site, but we do not link this to your Session ID or to any other personal or identifying information. 

**Affiliate ID:**   
If you entered our site by clicking a link on one of our affiliate web sites, we will attempt to store the ID of the affiliate as a cookie. We do this to ensure the affiliate receives proper credit for any subsequent order you might place. Your personally identifiable information **will not** be shared with any affiliates. 

Aside from the previously mentioned third parties involved in the processing of your order, we do not share your personally identifiable information with any other entities. In fact, **we will NEVER rent, sell or otherwise give your name to any other company or individual.** We utilize industry standard SSL encryption when accepting your credit card information during our online checkout process. In addition, we utilize the same encryption standard when transferring your credit card data to our internal fulfillment system. To further enhance our security measures, our fulfillment system is not accessible via the Internet and we delete from our web site database all credit card information within 72 hours of receipt. 

Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fradulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, Xandria.com will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. Xandria.com will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at Xandria.com while using our secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. To contact Xandria.com in the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, please e-mail us at [info@xandria.com](mailto:info@xandria.com). 

**Important Note** : The Fair Credit Billing Act does not cover liability for automatic debit cards or check cards. At Xandria.com, we recommend using a credit card rather than a debit or check card when purchasing products online. 

We may include links to other sites and if you decide to follow those links, we can't be responsible for the privacy policies and content of those sites. Generally, we will let you know when a link goes to another site. **Order information:**   
To make any changes to your order, please contact us via email or phone and we will be happy to assist you. 

**Email Subscriptions:**  
To subscribe or unsubscribe from our newsletter or promotional emails, please visit the Email Subscription page and use the available online forms. You may also unsubscribe via email by following the instructions printed at the bottom of every email. 

**Newsletter subscription:**  
To unsubscribe from our newsletter via email, please follow the instructions printed at the bottom of every newsletter. You may also unsubscribe online by using our Unsubscribe page. 

**Promotional E-Mail Lists:**   
To unsubscribe from our promotional e-mail lists via email, please follow the instructions printed at the bottom of each e-mail. You may also unsubscribe online by using our Unsubscribe page. 

**Catalog:**   
To remove your address from our mailing list, please send an email to [remove@xandria.com](mailto:remove@xandria.com) with your name and address. If you would like a confirmation that we have processed your request, your must explicitly ask for the confirmation in your email. Please understand that due to the lead time involved with these mailings, it is possible to receive an additional mailing after you have submitted your request. 

**Affiliates**  
Affiliates are other websites that have agreed to place a Xandria link or ad on their site in return for percentage-based compensation for all orders that originate from their site. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small data file that many Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk, determine your email address, or read cookie files created by other sites. Xandria uses cookies for only two purposes: to maintain your shopping basket and to track which ad you clicked to get to our site. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. 

**IP Address**   
When you are connected to the Internet, your computer has a unique Internet ID called an IP address. Most people that connect through a dial-up service, such as America Online, get a different IP address each time they login. Others might have a permanently assigned IP address, called a static IP address. It is difficult or impossible for a web site to collect personal information about you (i.e., your name, email address, etc.) from your IP address alone, though it is easier if you have a static IP address. 

**Session ID**   
A unique ID assigned each time someone visits an online store with a shopping basket system. Each store you visit will assign you a different ID. Many stores use a cookie to save your Session ID for re-use when you return to that same store. Most shoppers find it convenient that their shopping basket is maintained between visits but others find it objectionable and therefore turn cookies off. 

**SSL Encryption**   
A method by which information transmitted across the Internet is scrambled to the point where it's virtually indecipherable by anyone who should intercept the data before it reaches its destination. Most reputable online stores make use of SSL encryption to request credit card information and other sensitive data from their customers. Web pages where SSL encryption is activated are typically identified by a lock or key symbol displayed somewhere in your browser. Refer to your browser's documentation for the specific symbol and location. 

In compliance with the Federal Labeling and Record-Keeping Law (also known as 18 U.S.C. 2257), all models located within our domain were 18 years of age or older during the time of photography. All content and images are in full compliance with the requirements of 18 U.S.C. 2257 and associated regulations. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, wish to have information about you deleted, opt-out of mailings, or want to place an order via a method other than the Internet, you can contact us at: 

Lawrence Research Group  
5375 Procyon St, Suite 102  
Las Vegas, NV 89118 

Email: [info@xandria.com](mailto:info@xandria.com)  
Phone: 800-242-2823  
Fax: 702-895-6629 

Copyright 2006 Lawrence Research Group
